我不得不佩服你 哥们
I got to hand it to you, munch.
你想出来了个疯狂的主意
You came up with a ridiculous idea
而且让它还奏效了
And you made it work.
最好的是压根没人发现
The best part is nobody found out.
你们俩干的事被我发现了
You two are so busted.
太对不住了  我们本该
We're sorry. we should--
你到底知道了些什么
What do you know?
噢  你们直接侵犯了我的地盘
Oh, just that you completely space-invaded me.
如果你们要拿我最爱的梳子
If you are going to use my favorite hairbrush
去梳小丑的假发
To brush out a clown wig,
至少要刷完后把恶心的橙色头发
At least remove the nasty orange hair
都清除掉
When you're done.
对的 被你发现了
Yeah, you got us.
我们确实偷了你的梳子去梳小丑的假发套
We were stealing brushes and combing clown wigs
梳了一整个周末
All weekend.
真是火眼金睛啊
Totally busted.
千万别在这么干了
Just don't let it happen again.
给你 20 美元  帮我把那梳子弄到手
I'll give you 20 bucks if you can get me that brush.